音乐...
Music...
Música...
我
i
帕勃罗·迪亚兹（PabloDíaz）是...
Pablo Díaz is a ...
Pablo Díaz es un...
奇科（Chico），不是那么男孩，来自拉古纳·拉戈（Laguna Largo），有...
Chico, not so boy, from Laguna Largo, who had ...
Chico, ya no tan chico, de laguna larga, que tuvo...
实现自己的梦想，实现自己的梦想，演奏的可能性。
The possibility of living his dream, of fulfilling his dream, of playing.
la posibilidad de vivir su sueño, de cumplir su sueño, de jugar.
到职业足球，今天过着...
to professional football and that today is living a life that ...
al fútbol profesional y que hoy está viviendo una vida que...
他永远不会想象能够活着，而且他显然非常感谢...
that he would never have imagined to be able to live and that he is obviously very grateful for ...
que nunca se habría imaginado de poder vivir y que obviamente está muy agradecido por...
为了我们必须生活的一切，也感谢生活给我的一切，无论是好是坏。
For what we have to live and also grateful for all the learning that life gave me, both good and bad.
por lo que toca vivir y agradecido también de todos los aprendizajes que me dio la vida, tanto buenos como malos.
好吧，我们开始摇摇欲坠，仅与保罗·迪巴拉（Paulo Dybala）无关。
Well, we start the Seduls, nothing more and nothing less than with Paulo Dybala.
Bueno, arrancamos los seduls, nada más y nada menos que con Paulo Dybala.
嘉宾和真相保罗感谢您在家中收到了我们的接待。
Guest and the truth Paul thanks for having received us, for being here at home.
invitado y la verdad Pablo gracias por habernos recibido, por estar acá en tu casa.
一个地方。
A place.
Un placer.
很高兴与您同在。
A pleasure to be first and be here with you.
Un placer ser primero y estar acá con ustedes.
你好吗？
How are you?
¿Cómo estás?
你好吗？
How are you taking it?
¿Cómo la estás llevando?
受伤，恢复？
The injury, the recovery?
¿La lesión, la recuperación?
那怎么了？
How is that going?
¿Cómo va eso?
好吧，好吧。
Well, well.
Bien, bien.
现在有点安静。
Now a little quieter.
Ahora un poco más tranquilo.
开始是...
The beginning was ...
El principio fue...
显然，当我知道我要在外面的时候很难。
Hard obviously when I knew the time I was going to be outside.
Duro obviamente cuando supe el tiempo que iba a estar afuera.
在法庭外，我们与我们一起拥有的日历。
Outside the court for everything that came, the calendar we had with us.
fuera de la cancha por todo lo que se venía, el calendario que teníamos con nosotros.
与罗马相匹配的罗马，这就是一切...
With Rome, the selection matches, it was everything ...
Con la Roma, los partidos de la selección, era todo...
一切都很好，我感觉很好。
It was all very nice and I had been feeling very well.
Era todo muy lindo y yo me venía sintiendo muy bien.
从身体上讲，我在一年中的片刻中感到。
Physically I felt in a few moments of the year.
Físicamente me sentía en unos mejores momentos del año.
我看到了很多东西...
I was seeing everything a lot ...
Estaba viendo todo mucho...
最可爱的，以非常积极的方式，这比现在很冷...
Much cutest, in a very positive way, and it was a cold bucket than now ...
mucho más lindo, de manera muy positiva, y fue un baldazo a voz fría que ahora...
我已经吸收了它，并且正在努力尽快退还它。
I already assimilated it and I am working to return it as soon as possible.
ya lo asimilé y estoy trabajando para volverlo lo antes posible.
我在这个双重日期的前一天刚刚发生了什么，我刚刚发生了什么？
What generated that I had just happened to you in the previous date of this double date the selection with important matches?
¿Qué te generó que justo te haya pasado en la previa de esta doble fecha la selección con partidos importantes?
您如何承担想要成为并突然出现超越您而不是存在的事物的情况。
How you carried that situation of wanting to be and suddenly, for something that exceeds you, not being.
cómo llevaste esa situación de querer estar y que de pronto, por algo que te excede, no estar.
知道我要参加的事实是...
The fact of knowing that I was going to be in the selection was ...
El hecho de saber que iba a volver a estar en la selección era...
对我来说很漂亮，失去了我。
Beautiful for me to have lost me.
hermoso para mí de haberme perdido.
最后两个电话，正如我只告诉你，有时...
The last two calls and as I told you only, sometimes ...
las últimas dos convocatorias y como te dije recién, a veces...
我想知道离...
I wonder how close to ...
Me pregunto yo mismo de qué gusto tan cerca de...
旅行，能够穿上阿根廷衬衫。
of traveling, to be able to put on the Argentine shirt.
de viajar, de poder volver a ponerme la camiseta de Argentina.
我发生了一些事情，所以这在心理上非常困难。
Something happens to me, so it is very hard psychologically.
me pasa algo así, entonces es muy duro psicológicamente.
它使您清算，因为没有什么比在那里更美丽的了。
It liquidates you because there is nothing more beautiful than being there.
te liquida porque no hay nada más lindo que estar allá.
那是关于...
Then one is about ...
Entonces uno trata de...
首先开始在心理层面上工作，这样我就不会这样丢下你，因为以后，好吧，那就...
To start working at the psychological level first so that I will not throw you so down because later, well, then ...
de empezarlo a trabajar a nivel psicológico primero para que no te tire tan abajo porque después, bueno, pues...
对病变的影响很大。
Influence a lot about the lesion.
influenciar muchísimo sobre la lesión.
你有很多事情吗？
Did you get a lot of this time?
¿Te bajoneó mucho esta vez?
总是一样，总是在NEA下，很小或...
Always, the same always, under Nea, be small or ...
Siempre, igual siempre, bajo nea, sea chiquito o sea...
伤害加重。
The injury is aggravated.
Se agrande la lesión.
一个小女孩，说，运气不好
A little girl, say, bad luck with
Una pequeña, digamos, mala suerte con
因此，这就是我告诉你的，有时候你走得如此接近...
Therefore, that is what I told you, that sometimes you go so close to going that ...
Por eso, eso es lo que te decía, que a veces pasas tan cerca de ir que...
内里的一个人说，我不希望他们认为...
Also one inside says, I don't want them to think that ...
También uno por dentro dice, no quiero que piensen que...
我不想成为，或者也许我什么都没有，但我说我有话。
I don't want to be or maybe I have nothing but I say I have something.
que no quiero estar o que a lo mejor no tengo nada pero digo que tengo algo.
您最想要的是参加国家队，我们全年都准备比赛。
One what you want most is to be in the national team, we prepare throughout the year to be able to play the few games there are.
uno lo que más quiere es estar en la selección, nos preparamos durante todo el año para poder jugar los pocos partidos que hay.
在这一年中，什么都没有发生。
During the year and nothing, that happens right there.
durante el año y nada, que pase justo ahí.
他们很大。
They are very large.
Son bajos muy grandes.
和那些在通话之前，您会引起人们的关注。
And those prior to the calls you live with some attention.
Y las previas a las convocatorias las vivís con cierta atención.
用存在的电压。
With the voltage of being.
Con la tensión de estar.
并不是说如果我会发生什么事情。
Not that if something was going to happen to me.
No de que si me iba a pasar algo.
我很幸运，我学会了安静地玩，不要以为我
I am luck that I learned to play quietly, not to think that I
Tengo la suerte de que con el tiempo aprendí a jugar tranquilo, de no pensar en que me
可能会发生一些新的事情，这是我在职业生涯中工作的事情。
Something new can happen, it is something that I worked during my career.
puede llegar a pasar algo nuevo, es algo que trabajé durante mi carrera.
但是显然，我们都说出那个刺耳的话，好吧...
But obviously we are all with that thorn of saying, well ...
Pero obviamente que todos estamos con esa espinita de decir, bueno...
我要成为否则我不会。
I'm going to be or I'm not going to be.
Voy a estar o no voy a estar.
有很多球员。
There are many players.
Hay muchos jugadores.
他们在全国和欧洲的选举中表现出色。
that they are doing very well in the elections both nationally and European.
que lo están haciendo muy bien en las elecciones tanto a nivel nacional como a nivel europeo.
比赛是如此之大，以至于必须超过100％。
The competition is so large that one has to be more than 100% to be.
La competencia es tan grande que uno tiene que estar más del 100% para estar.
事实生活有点紧张。
The fact is lived with a little tension.
se vive con un poquito de tensión el hecho ese.
而且您在上一篇中说话，我不知道，您在上一篇中意识到，我不知道是直接使用Scaloni，Mana还是与...
And you are talking in the previous one, I do not know, you are realizing in the previous one, I do not know if direct with Scaloni or with mana or with ...
y lo vas hablando en la previa, no sé, te vas dando cuenta en la previa, no sé si directo con Scaloni o con Mana o con...
与他们中的任何一个。
With any of them.
con cualquiera de ellos.
我在球场上的水平很多，我认为，我认为...
I look a lot at my level on the court, to say, well, I think ...
miro mucho mi nivel dentro de la cancha, de decir, bueno, creo que...
如果我那样，我将成为。
If I'm like that, I'm going to be.
Si estoy así, voy a estar.
我知道我会以我的素质信任我。
I know that I will be, I know they trust me, in my qualities.
Sé que voy a estar, sé que confían en mí, en mis cualidades.
如果我处于最佳水平，显然以后...
If I am on my best level to be, obviously one later ...
Si estoy en mi mejor nivel para poder estar, obviamente que uno después...
您必须知道这是一个教练的决定，但是如果您要做得很好，那就让您放心地说，好吧...
You have to know that it is a coach's decision, but if you are going to do things well, it leaves you the peace of mind of saying, well ...
Tiene que saber que es una decisión del entrenador, pero si vas a hacer las cosas bien te deja la tranquilidad de decir, bueno...
我正在做正确的事情，如果我不是因为有人做得更好。
I'm doing things right, if I'm not because someone is doing better.
estoy haciendo las cosas bien, si no estoy es porque alguien lo está haciendo mejor.
您知道自己付出了一切，保持镇定。
You stay calm with knowing that you gave everything to be.
te quedas tranquilo con saber que diste todo para estar.
显然，这样的事情发生在您身上...
Obviously something like this happens to you ...
Obviamente que si te pasa algo así...
因为您的故事与选择非常特别，因为您在世界上特定的时刻被火着。
Because apart your story with the selection is very particular because you were marked on fire in specific moments of the world.
Porque aparte tu historia con la selección es muy particular porque quedaste marcado a fuego en momentos puntuales del mundo.
例如，没有玩很多分钟，人们会在关键时刻记住您，然后它不必在América中，就像...
For example, without having played many minutes, people remembers you at key moments, then it didn't have to be in the Copa América, it's like ...
por ejemplo, sin haber jugado muchísimos minutos, la gente te recuerda por momentos claves, después no te tocó estar en la Copa América, es como que...
它有摇摆的是您与阿根廷性爱的故事。
It has swing is your story with Argentine sex.
tiene vaivén es tu historia con la sexo argentina.
是的，在决赛中我发生的事情也很少。
Yes, it was a bit also what happened to me in the final, that I entered very little.
Sí, fue un poco también lo que me pasó en la finalísima, que entré muy poco.
你有目标吗？
And did you have a goal?
¿Y te tocó hacer un gol?
而且，除了游戏是侦察赢得的事实之外，我必须做一个目标，因为这是一场令人难以置信的比赛。
And that I had to make a goal, beyond the fact that the game was recontra won, because it was an incredible game.
Y que me tocó hacer un gol, más allá de que el partido estaba recontra ganado, porque fue un partido increíble.
我可以是那些比赛，然后在世界杯上那样。
I could be those games and then in the World Cup it was like that.
Pude estar esos partidos y después en el Mundial fue así.
我玩的时间不多，我带着正确的方式到达。
I did not play much, I arrived with the right.
No jugué mucho, llegué con lo justo.
我也受到了重要的伤害，但我无法到达。
I had also had an important injury, but I couldn't arrive.
También había tenido una lesión importante, pero no pude llegar.
我可以到达，然后...
I could arrive and then ...
Pude llegar y después...
知道一个人多次履行的角色，您必须支持，提供帮助。
Knowing the role that one fulfills many times, that you have to support, help.
sabiendo del rol que uno cumple muchas veces, de que hay que en momentos así apoyar, ayudar.
...从碰到你的地方...
... from where it touches you ...
...desde donde te toque...
而且，如果技术人员打电话给您，那么您已经100％准备好了。
And if the technician calls you, you are 100% ready.
Y si el técnico te llama, estás 100% listo.
所以，我知道...
So, I knew that ...
Entonces, yo sabía que...
在某个时候，我要碰我，我必须全力集中到触动我的东西，这是发生的...
At some point I was going to touch me and I had to be full concentrated for what touched me and well, it happened ...
en algún momento me iba a tocar y tenía que estar full concentrado para lo que me toque y bueno, se dio...
仅仅是决赛，只有更重要的是。
Nothing more and nothing less than in the final.
nada más y nada menos que en la final.
您没有经济上的收入，您以与人的爱赢得了他。
What you didn't earn economically you won him with love with people.
Lo que no ganaste económicamente lo ganaste de cariño con la gente.
由于一分钟，您进入罗马心脏并不困难...
It was not difficult for you to enter the heart of Rome because of the minute one ...
No te costó entrar en el corazón de Roma porque ya del minuto uno...
您的演示文稿转变为世界，图像，因为很难看到这样的演讲。
Your presentation turned the world, the image, because it is difficult to see such a presentation.
Tu presentación dio la vuelta al mundo, la imagen, porque es difícil ver una presentación así.
但是他们仍然爱你。
But then they still loved you.
Pero después te siguieron queriendo.
托蒂最近说...
Toti, recently, said that ...
Toti, hace poco, dijo que...
就像来自来自南部的其他团队...
It's like coming from other teams from Italy, South ...
Es como que viniendo de otros equipos de Italia, del sur...
在北部时期，您来到这里进入中心进入，但是...
And at the time of the north you came here to the center and entered but ...
y en su momento del norte viniste acá al centro y entraste pero...
人民很自然。
very naturally in the people.
muy naturalmente en la gente.
您感到惊讶的是您进入的能力如何吗？
Did you surprise how well you entered?
¿Te sorprendió lo bien que entraste?
是的，离开尤文图斯并去另一支球队并不容易。
Yes, it is not easy to leave Juventus and go to another team.
Sí, no es fácil salir de Juventus y ir a otro equipo.
来自意大利，从第一天开始爱你。
from Italy and that people from day one love you.
de Italia y que la gente ya desde el primer día te quiera.
这并不容易，这是一个竞争激烈的俱乐部。
It is not easy, it is a club with a lot of competition.
No es fácil, es un club con mucha competencia.
其中，我对第一天的热爱感到非常惊讶。
Among, I was very surprised by the love of the first day.
Entre sí, me sorprendió muchísimo el cariño del primer día.
我三年前，我活着。
I am three years ago and that I live it.
ya hace tres años que estoy y que lo vivo.
我一直都住在罗马的球迷们与之一起去的地方
that I always live it, where we go with Rome the fans are
que lo vivo siempre, donde vamos con la Roma los hinchas son
在各种方面，与我的同事们一起，这座城市都有一定程度的狂热主义。
Incredible in every way, also with my colleagues there is a level of fanaticism in this city.
increíble en todo sentido, también con mis compañeros hay un nivel de fanatismo en esta ciudad.
非常棒，与阿根廷非常相似。
Very great that is very similar to that of Argentina.
muy grande que es muy parecido al de Argentina.
而且，好吧，与我在一起，人们变得非常喜欢，事实是我总是试图...
And, well, with me people became very fond of and the truth is that I always try to ...
Y, bueno, conmigo la gente se encariñó mucho y la verdad que siempre trato de...
返回他的爱，因为事实是对我和...
To return to him the love, because the truth is that it is very great, both for me and ...
De devolverle de cualquier forma el cariño, porque la verdad es que es muy grande, tanto para mí como...
为我的家人。
For my family.
para mi familia.
我的意思是，当我在房子里走来走去时，您也可以告诉您奥里亚娜。
I mean, you can tell you as Oriana also when I walk around the house.
O sea, te lo puede decir Oriana también cuando ando por la casa.
他们给他感情。
They give him affection.
Le dan afecto.
他们给他感情，是的。
They give him affection, yes.
Que le dan afecto, sí.
在阿根廷，您来生活了那种激情，还是为什么很小？
In Argentina you came to live that passion or why were you very small?
¿En Argentina llegaste a vivir esa pasión o porque eras muy chico?
好吧，它在一个非常重要的俱乐部中触动了您，但是当时我属于第二类，或者您开始​​住在这里疯狂
Well it touched you in a very important club but I was in the second category at that time or you started living here that madness
bueno te tocó en un club muy importante pero que estaba en la segunda categoría en ese momento o lo empezaste a vivir acá esa locura
是的，我在研究所很少，是的，因为那年对我们来说很特别。
Yes, I was little in the institute, yes, because also that year was very particular to us.
Sí, yo estuve poco en el instituto, sí, porque también ese año fue muy particular a nosotros.
对于那一年的期望，这不是很好。
It was not very good for the expectations in that year.
no fue muy bien para las expectativas que había en ese año.
我当时17岁，然后离开了俱乐部。
I was 17 years old, then I left the club.
Yo tenía 17 años, entonces salía del club.
对我来说，这是一个新的挑战，是对火的热爱。
It is a new challenge for me, the love of fires.
Es un reto nuevo para mí, el cariño de los incendios.
令人难以置信的是，当他们玩劣等时，我去了法庭看比赛，所以一切都很好。
Incredible, I went to the court to see the games when they played inferior ones, so it was all very nice.
Increíble, yo iba a la cancha a ver los partidos cuando jugaban inferiores, entonces era todo muy lindo.
这大约是我的13年和真相...
Here is about 13 years that I am and the truth that ...
Acá ya hace como 13 años que estoy y la verdad que...
一开始我在巴勒莫收到的爱，当时我经历了尤文图斯，现在去了罗马。
The love I received in Palermo at the beginning, when I went through Juventus and now for Rome.
el cariño que recibí en Palermo al principio, cuando pasé por Juventus y ahora por la Roma.
人们总是和我在一起...
People really that with me always ...
la gente la verdad que conmigo siempre...
这是我和我的家人的表演。
It was a show for me and my family.
Fue un espectáculo tanto para mí como para mi familia.
我认为这种认可是最美丽的事物之一。
And that recognition I think is one of the most beautiful things than a ...
Y ese reconocimiento creo que es una de las cosas más lindas que un...
运动员可以尊重您或受到不同球迷的喜爱，我认为这是一样的。
Athlete can have, to respect you or be loved by different fans, I think it is the same.
deportista puede tener, que te respeten o ser querido por diferentes hinchadas, creo que es lo mismo.
在这里，他们爱其他俱乐部吗？
Does that happen to you here that they love you of other clubs?
¿Eso te pasa acá que te quieren hincha de otros clubes?
是的，让我们看看，我不知道这个词是那个词。
Yes, let's see, I don't know if the word is that.
Sí, a ver, no sé si la palabra es esa.
他们打招呼，一切都很好。
They greet and everything is fine.
saludan y está todo bien.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
是否为尤文图斯效力都没关系。
It doesn't matter if you played for Juventus.
No importa que haya jugado para Juventus.
这是罗马的游戏，因为我的游戏已被认可或我在意大利所做的。
It is a game for Rome, as my game is recognized or what I did in Italy.
Es un juego para la Roma, como que reconocen a lo mejor mi juego o lo que yo hice en Italia.
或我所说的那样，我所说的就是什么...
Or what I won and that, as I say, for me is what ...
o lo que gané y que eso, como digo, para mí es lo...
最美丽的认可。
The most beautiful recognition.
el reconocimiento de lo más lindo.
在您的职业生涯中，您是来自意大利的标志性球员，多年来在不同的团队中。
For your career you were an iconic player from Italy for so many years in different teams.
Por tu carrera quedaste como un jugador icónico de Italia por tantos años en diferentes equipos.
当您退休时，当您不参加专业活动时，您就想到了要居住的头脑，如果在这里，如果在阿根廷或其他方面。
When you retire, when you are not in professional activity, you have thought of your head where you are going to live, if here, if Argentina or other.
Cuando te retires, cuando no estés en actividad profesional, tenés pensado en tu cabeza dónde vas a vivir, si acá, si Argentina o otro lado.
不要想，因为这已经是您的国家，这也是如此多年，是的
not to think because it is already the truth that it is your country this also after so many years yes yes yes
que no pensar pues ya la verdad que es tu país este también después de tantos años sí sí sí sí
我已经考虑过，但我不知道，因为起初我说不...
I have thought about it, but I don't know, because at first I said no ...
Lo he pensado, pero no sé, porque al principio decía que no...
现在我告诉你我不知道。
Now I tell you I don't know.
Ahora te digo no sé.
这也取决于许多事情，工作，您想做什么。
It also depends on many things, work, what you want to do.
También depende de muchas cosas, el trabajo, lo que quiera hacer.
和我的家人在一起，如果我有孩子要哭泣的地方，也许明天在阿根廷
With my family, where maybe tomorrow if I have children where I would like to be cried, if here in Argentina
con mi familia, donde a lo mejor el día de mañana si tengo hijos donde me gustaría más que se críen, si acá en Argentina
我不知道。
I don't know.
No sé.
您打算作为父亲说话吗？
Do you plan to be a father, for what you said?
¿Tienes pensado ser padre, por lo que dijiste?
我会喜欢的，是的。
I would love it, yes.
Me encantaría, sí.
我喜欢。
I'd love to.
Me encantaría.
他们尊重您社会的专业时刻。
They are respecting the professional moments of your society.
Están respetando los momentos profesionales de tu sociedad.
不，不。
No no.
No, no.
事实是我们正在寻找。
The truth is that we are looking.
La verdad es que estamos buscando.
我们正在等待...
We are waiting for ...
Estamos esperando que...
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
他们正在搜索中。
They are in search.
Están en la búsqueda.
我们正在搜索。
We are in search.
Estamos en la búsqueda.
假设我们必须实现目标。
We have to make the goal, let's say.
Tiene que hacerse el gol, digamos.
我们正在等待您抓住。
We are waiting for you to grab.
Estamos esperando que agarre.
他们已经采取了所有步骤，但是我们有经验，婚姻...
They already made all the steps, but we were with experience, marriage ...
Ya hicieron todos los pasos, pero quedamos con vivencia, casamiento...
奥里亚纳（Oriana）把我放在一起的第一天。
Oriana put me the first day of the together.
Oriana me puso el primer día de los juntos.
首先，我们结婚了，然后我会从一开始就寻求。
First we got married and then I would have sought from the beginning.
Primero nos casamos y después yo hubiese buscado desde el principio.
但是，奥里亚纳一直想要
But well, Oriana always wanted
Pero bueno, Oriana siempre quiso
让我们结婚...但是要特别，宝贝，宝贝...不，不，什么，什么，
Let's get married ... but be particular, baby, baby ... no, no, whatever, whatever comes
que nos casemos... sino que sea particular, nene, nena... no, no, lo que sea, lo que venga
但是现在我希望它应该得到。
But now it is at that time that I hope it should be shown.
Pero ahora está en ese momento de que ojalá que se debería mostrar.
我也是一个老太太，但是当我们发现自己时，我们就在...
An old woman, me too, but when we find ourselves, we are about ...
una vieja mucho, yo también, pero cuando nos encontramos tratamos de...
搜索以查看您今天是否可以得到。
Search to see if you can get today.
de buscar para ver si puede llegar hoy.
而且您的体育职业的未来也可以想象，这将有所限制。
And the future of your sports career also imagine that it will be a bit conditioned by this.
Y el futuro de tu carrera deportiva también me imagino que será un poco condicionado por esto.
在某个时候返回阿根廷，我不知道世界上是否还有其他联盟正在审理。
At some point return to Argentina, I don't know if there is any other league in the world that has been pending.
en algún momento volver a Argentina, no sé si hay alguna otra liga del mundo que te haya quedado pendiente.
我呆在一个欧洲的想法中，您会在这里玩。
I stay with an idea of ​​Europe that you say, here I would have played.
Te quedo con una idea de Europa que decís, acá hubiese jugado.
还是发生在您身上？
Or does that happen to you?
¿O no se te pasa eso por la cabeza?
那给你带来了阴谋。
That has given you intrigue.
Que te haya dado intriga.
起初不是。
At first not.
Al principio no.
起初我一直想成为...
At first I always wanted to be ...
Al principio siempre quise estar...
在意大利。
In Italy.
en Italia.
我一直喜欢它，我感到非常确定。
I always liked it, I felt very identified.
Siempre me gustó, me sentía muy identificado.
使用系列A。
With series A.
con la serie A.
今天，我相信联盟就像是一个冠军，我对特征并不感到舒适。
Today I believe that the League is like a championship in which I have not felt comfortable by characteristics.
Hoy creo que la Liga es como un campeonato en el que yo a lo mejor me he sentido cómodo por características.
那一刻，当我说我要采访你时，人们想知道阿根廷足球吗？
It was a moment that people, when I said I was going to interview you, was wondering, is Argentine football?
Era un momento que la gente, cuando dije que te iba a entrevistar, me preguntaba ¿es fútbol argentino?
事实是不是在第一次玩，知道体育场...
And the truth is not to have played in the first, know the stadiums ...
Y la verdad que no haber jugado en la primera, conocer los estadios...
是的，我在脑海中有。
Yes, I have it in my mind.
Sí, lo tengo en mi mente.
我不知道这是否会发生。
I don't know if it's going to happen.
No sé si va a pasar.
精确的。
Exact.
Exacto.
我不知道它是否会发生，但没有。
I don't know if it was going to happen, but no.
No sé si iba a pasar, pero no.
我不知道这是否会发生。
I don't know if it was going to happen.
No sé si iba a pasar.
墙壁，同样的压力。
Walls, the same, a little pressure.
Paredes, igual, un poquito de presión.
墙壁每天都会压我。
Walls presses me every day.
Paredes me presiona todos los días.
它开了你吗？
Does it prescribe you?
¿Te presiona?
帕雷斯，每天用嘴按你。
Parés, presses you with mouth every day.
Parés, te presiona con boca todos los días.
您如何看待？
And what do you think of that?
¿Y vos qué piensas de eso?
不，真的，正如我刚刚告诉你的...
No, that really, as I just told you ...
No, eso la verdad que, como te acabo de decir...
我很想在阿根廷玩。
I would love to play in Argentina.
Me encantaría jugar en Argentina.
我也知道粉丝。
I know the fans too.
Sé que los hinchas también.
他们希望从研究所开始，我对那个非常大的俱乐部有爱...
From institute they want it to be, I have a love for the very big club that was the one that ...
de instituto quieren que esté, tengo un cariño por el club muy grande que fue el que...
他使我的职业长大并到达欧洲，这要归功于他们。
He made my career grown up and arrived in Europe is thanks to them.
hizo que mi carrera haya crecido y haya llegado a Europa es gracias a ellos.
事实是，我考虑返回阿根廷。
And the truth is that I think about returning to Argentina.
y la verdad que lo pienso en volver a Argentina.
好，在某个时候。
Ok, at some point.
Ok, en algún momento.
例如，当您说我会得到稀有皮肤，像海湾一样肿胀。
When you said, for example, I get a rare skin, the swollen like a gulf.
Cuando dijiste, por ejemplo, se me pone la piel rara, el hinchado como un golfo.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
不，不，是的，让我们看看粉丝们。
No, no, yes, let's see, the fans do.
No, no, sí, a ver, los hinchas sí.
我有时会在Instagram上看到...
I sometimes see on Instagram ...
Yo a veces veo en Instagram...
显然，当我还是个男孩，我读过的时候，有我的照片。
There are photos of me when I was a boy, I read, or those things, obviously.
Hay fotos mías de cuando era chico, lo de Lea, o esas cosas, obviamente.
粉丝们写信给我，这很好，因为永远不会...
The fans write to me and it's nice because never ...
Los hinchas me escriben y es lindo porque nunca...
我从未去过法庭观看BOCA比赛。
I never went to the court to watch a Boca match.
Nunca fui a la cancha a ver un partido de boca.
即使，昨天我们只是以假日为主题给予，因为第一场比赛在迈阿密。
And even, well, yesterday we were just giving by the holiday theme, because the first game plays in Miami.
Y incluso, bueno, ayer justo estábamos dando goleadas por el tema de las vacaciones, porque el primer partido juega en Miami.
我想我想和他一起去看看约翰与本菲卡的比赛。
And I wanted me to stay with him to go see that John's game with Benfica, I think.
Y quería que me quede con él para ir a ver el partido de ese Juan con Benfica, creo.
确切地说，俱乐部芒内。
Exactly, club munnel.
Exacto, Múnel de Clubes.
我告诉他，我不知道为什么我不知道我会在这种情况下做什么。
I told him that I didn't know why I don't know what I'm going to do for the occasions.
Le dije que no sabía porque tampoco sé qué voy a hacer para las ocasiones.
但是，好吧，让我们看看，我不知道，事实是，我不知道，回到阿根廷的大门，显然我离开了...
But well, let's see, I don't know, the truth is that I don't know, the door to return to Argentina, obviously I leave it ...
Pero bueno, a ver, no sé, la verdad que no sé, la puerta para volver a Argentina, lo obvio que la dejo...
开放是因为，让我们看看，我会喜欢的，但我仍然不知道。
Open because, let's see, I would love it, but I still don't know.
abierta porque, a ver, me encantaría, pero todavía no sé.
或者您不能保证您不知道您是否会遵守的事情。
Or that you can't promise something you don't know if you're going to comply.
o que no se puede prometer algo que no sabes si vas a cumplir.
我问你，你爱吗，与博卡有的你，还是它逐渐与您联系在一起，或者当您还是男孩时那是什么？
I ask you, do you love and with Boca you have it or is it something that was gradually linked to you or what was it when you were a boy?
Te pregunto, ¿el cariño y con boca vos lo tenés o es algo que se te fue ligando de a poco o que era lo que era cuando eras chico?
是的，我的老人是粉丝。
Yes, my old man was a fan.
Sí, mi viejo era fanático.
我的老人是博卡粉丝，有三个孩子。
My old man was a Boca fan and had three children.
Mi viejo era fanático de Boca y tuvo tres hijos.
最伟大的两个来自河流之一和独立之一。
And the two greatest came out of one of River and one of Independiente.
y los dos más grandes le salieron de uno de River y uno de Independiente.
我是最小的人，然后我到处走到了博卡
And I was the youngest then it took me everywhere that came to Boca
y yo era el más chico entonces me llevaba a todos lados partido que venía a Boca
啊，他担心第三个也不来自他的团队。
Ah, he was afraid that the third is not from his team either.
Ah, tenía miedo que el tercero tampoco sea de su equipo.
但是，十年后，我去了研究所。
But well, after 10 years I went to institute.
Pero bueno, yo después de los 10 años me fui a instituto.
它已经是更多的研究所，但是当博卡与科尔多巴的一支球队比赛时
And it was already more institute, but when Boca played against a team from Córdoba
y ya era más instituto, pero yo cuando Boca jugaba contra algún equipo de Córdoba
我们一直在球场上。
We were always on the court.
íbamos siempre a la cancha.
完美的。
Perfect.
Perfecto.
哪几天赢得了什么比赛？
What game won the other day?
¿Qué partido ganó el otro día?
实际上，索尔在罗马做什么，在这里做什么目标？
Actually, what classic, what goal did Saul did in Rome or not here?
En realidad, ¿qué clásico, qué golazo hizo Saúl en Roma o no acá?
极好的。
Incredible.
Increíble.
而且我们一直在炎热，因为他开始了很多。
And we had been fucking in heat because he was starting a lot.
Y encima habíamos estado jodiendo en la entrada en calor porque él estaba partiendo mucho.
所以。
So.
Así.
不，到第一把棍子。
No, to the first stick.
No, al primer palo.
到另一个棍子。
To the other stick.
Al otro palo.
然后我们说...
Then we said ...
Entonces le decíamos...
帕特亚（Patea）更多地是男孩的优点，他的优点是他实现的目标。
Patea more to the second, the merit of mine of the boys, the merit of him who made a goal.
Patea más al segundo, el mérito mío de los chicos, el mérito de él que hizo un golazo.
但是刚刚拍摄的是我告诉他，打开并推开了脚。
But it had just been filmed that I told him, opened and pushed his foot.
Pero justo había quedado filmado que yo le decía, abrí y empujo el pie.
然后我他妈的他说，嘿，我必须张开你的脚。
And then I fuck him and said, hey, I had to open your foot.
Y después lo jodí y le decía, oye, te tenía que abrir el pie.
他离开了自己的身份，并做了另一个。
He left for his identity and does another.
Partía a su idépocas y hace otro.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
守门员吃了它。
That the goalkeeper had eaten it.
Que el arquero se lo había comido.
如果没有，这是一个目标。
If not, it was a goal.
Si no, era un golazo.
您如何看待Mati？
How do you see Mati?
¿Cómo lo ves a Mati?
好的？
GOOD?
¿Bien?
不，好。
No, good.
No, bien.
适应俱乐部并不容易...
It is not easy to adapt to a club ...
No es fácil adaptarse a un club...
因此，我认为他有很多素质。
Thus I think he has many qualities.
Así yo creo que él tiene muchas cualidades.
正如您与墙壁交谈以及与他交谈时，Leandro也必须发生同样的事情，对吗？
And just as you speak with walls and with him when you were to go, the same must have happened with Leandro, right?
Y así como vos hablas hablado con Paredes y con él cuando te estabas por ir, lo mismo debe haber pasado con Leandro, ¿no?
好吧，你说我们想继续。
Well, you said we wanted to continue.
Bueno, dijiste que queríamos seguir.
我告诉他，但我来了。
I told him, but I came.
Yo le dije, pero vine.
六个月前，我们决定留下，您现在不会离开。
Six months ago we decided to stay, you will not leave now.
Hace seis meses decidimos de quedarnos, no te vas a ir ahora.
他打你。
He hit you back.
Te pegó a la vuelta.
是的，它非常接近。
Yes, it was very close.
Sí, estuvo muy cerca.
我告诉他，坚持，不要去。
I told him, hold on, don't go yet.
Yo le dije, aguanta, no te vayas todavía.
再待一年。
Stay another year.
Quédate un año más.
我们去世界杯，然后看到。
We go to the World Cup and then we see.
Vamos al Mundial y después vemos.
我们去世界杯，然后看到。
We go to the World Cup and then we see.
Vamos al Mundial y después vemos.
不，之后我要和你谈谈。
No, I'm going to talk to you another good after.
No, que te voy a hablar otro bueno del después.
显然，一个...
Obviously, one ...
Obviamente, uno...
有时他说话，但是中间有很多事情，甚至是他的整个家庭。
Sometimes he says things, but there are many things in the middle, even his whole family.
A veces dice las cosas, pero hay muchas cosas en el medio, incluso toda su familia.
但很明显我想让他知道...
But obvious that I wanted him to know ...
Pero obvio que yo quería que se que...
显然，逻辑。
Obviously, logical.
Obvio, lógico.
它使它变得相反。
And it makes it the reverse.
Y encima la hace la inversa.
然后他说，当你回来时，他带你去找你。
Then he says that when you come back he takes you to you.
Después dice que cuando vuelves te lleva a vos.
显示？
¿Showed?
¿Viste?
他想带你。
He wants to take you.
Te quiere llevar puesto.
他在所有采访中总是让我进入中间。
He in all interviews always puts me in the middle.
Él en todas las entrevistas siempre me mete en el medio.
我告诉他，布鲁多（Boludo），有一点。
I told him, boludo, for a little.
Yo le dije, boludo, para un poco.
他在确认我。
He is confirming me.
Me está confirmitiendo.
他承受着很大的压力。
He is getting a lot of pressure.
Está metiendo mucha presión.
逻辑。
Logical.
Lógico.
我们有几个游戏和部分与您有关。
We have a couple of games and sections to do with you.
Tenemos un par de juegos y secciones para hacer con vos.
因为除了足球外，您喜欢时尚，并且参加了不同的时尚活动。
Because you like fashion apart from football and you were in different fashion events.
Porque a vos aparte del fútbol te gusta mucho la moda y estuviste en diferentes eventos de moda.
厚的。
Thick.
Grosos.
或者没有，外观不同。
Or no, with different looks.
O no, con diferentes looks.
显示？
¿Showed?
¿Viste?
最近，Polloálvarez与Rodrigo de Dusta播放了毒气。
Recently the Pollo Álvarez talk viralized with Rodrigo de Dusta.
Hace poco se viralizó la charla del pollo Álvarez con Rodrigo de Polvo.
在某些外观和其他外观中都选择了。
which was there selected in some looks and others.
que estuvo ahí seleccionada en unos looks y demás.
我们将让您看到他的一双外观。
We are going to make you see a pair of looks of him.
Vamos a hacerte ver un par de looks de él.
来自罗德里？
From Rodri?
¿De Rodri?
根据您的标准。
According to your criteria.
Según tu criterio.
您说您喜欢时尚，然后他们会让您看到您的。
That you said that you like fashion and then they will make you see yours.
que vos dijiste que te gusta la moda y después van a hacerte ver looks tuyos.
您将进行分数。
You will go on a score.
Irás a poner un puntaje.
现在是怎么回事。
Now how it is.
Ahora cómo está.
您想开始哪一个？
Which one do you want to start?
¿Con cuál querés arrancar?
我们将从下车的保罗开始。
We are going to start with Paul, who got very up.
Vamos a arrancar con De Paul, que se puso muy arriba.
我总是这么说。
I always said this.
Yo siempre dije esto.
我讨厌这些游戏。
I hate these games.
Los odio estos juegos.
你喜欢时尚吗？
Do you like fashion or not?
¿Te gusta la moda o no?
是的，我喜欢时尚。
Yes, I love fashion.
Sí, la moda me encanta.
好吧，最后，胜利。
Well, last, throw the triumph.
Bueno, de última, tirá la triunfa.
他说这是十个。
He says this is ten, for example.
Él dice que este es diez, por ejemplo.
他和鸡说了。
With the chicken he said that.
Con el pollo dijo eso.
嗯...还不错。
Ehhh ... that is not bad.
Ehhh... Ese no está mal.
可以看，这不是我的风格，而是因为他的风格并不糟糕。
It is, to see, it is not my style, but because of the style he has it is not bad.
Es, a ver, no es mi estilo, pero por el estilo que él tiene no está mal.
你会穿吗？
Would you wear that?
¿Vos te pondrías eso?
不，我不。
No, I don't.
No, yo no.
我也不会说。
I wouldn't put it either.
Este tampoco te lo pondría.
这是不可能的，对吗？
It's impossible, right?
Es imposible, ¿no?
但是另一个很好。
But the other is fine.
Pero el otro está bien.
另一个很好。
The other is fine.
El otro está bien.
我喜欢另一个。
I like the other.
El otro me gusta.
许多颜色都可以吗？
Many colors are fine or not?
¿Muchos colores están bien o no?
我没有多种颜色。
I am not of many colors.
Yo no soy de muchos colores.
你爱黑色。
You love black.
Vos amas de negro.
他说他去了夏天。
And he said he goes to summer.
Y él dijo que va para el verano.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
夏天。
Summer.
Verano.
我不喜欢鞋子，但是路加很好。
I don't like shoes, but Luke is fine.
No me gustan las zapas, pero Luke está bien.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
我会再放一个Zapa。
I would have put another zapa.
Lo hubiese puesto otra zapa.
完美的。
Perfect.
Perfecto.
那是他的。
Those are his.
Esos son los de él.
例如，您再看一下。
You, for example, have another look.
Vos, por ejemplo, tenés otro look.
例如，这很好...
For example, this is fine ...
Por ejemplo, este es bien...
但这是经典的，这是一件西装。
But that is classic, it's a suit.
Pero ese es clásico, es un traje.
但是也有意大利学校。
But there is Italian school too.
Pero ahí hay escuela italiana también.
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
当您到达时，他们抓住了您并告诉您，您必须在这里穿着这样的衣服。
When you arrived, they grabbed you and told you, here you have to dress like this.
A vos cuando llegaste, te agarraron y te dijeron, acá hay que vestirse así.
不，我经历了很多...
No, I went through many ...
No, yo pasé por muchos...
对于许多服装的心情，您对一切。
For many clothing mood, you of everything.
Por muchos mood de ropa, usted de todo.
起初，我使用了更多，更紧绷的身体，然后再使用一点...
At first I used the body a little more, more tight, then a little more ...
Al principio usé un poco más al cuerpo, más apretado, después un poco más...
超大。
Oversize.
例如，这更肌肉发达，更多的比赛。
This, for example, is more muscular, a little more play.
Esta, por ejemplo, es más musculosa, un poquito más jugada.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
是的，碰巧的是，只是...
Yes, it happens that, well, just that ...
Sí, pasa que, bueno, justo esa...
我不得不拍一张竞选的照片，所以就是这样，但是...
I had to take a picture of a campaign, so it was like that, but ...
Tenía que hacer una foto de una campaña, entonces era así, pero...
我不会在街上那样出去。
I don't go out like that on the street.
Yo no salgo así en la calle.
不，我认为这是最后一个标志性的，你是...
No, and the last iconic I think it was this, you are ...
No, y la última icónica creo que fue este, igual estás...
是的。
That yes.
Ese sí.
投资组合。
That of the portfolio.
El de la cartera.
关于钱包有一些批评，但这是外观的一部分。
There were a couple of criticisms about the wallet but it was part of the look.
Ahí hubo un par de críticas sobre la cartera pero era parte del look.
他们说，这是钱包，你把它放了。
They said, it is wallet, you banked it.
Dijeron, va cartera, te la bancaste.
是的，没有戏剧。
Yes, there is no drama.
Sí, no hay drama.
奥里亚纳，你认为吗？
Oriana, do you think?
Oriana, ¿opina?
是的，百分百。
Yes, one hundred percent.
Sí, cien por cien.
它建议您吗？
Does it advise you?
¿Te asesora?
不，我问他。
No, I ask him.
No, yo le pregunto.
例如，如果前几天我不得不让我尝试衣服...
For example, if the other day I had to make me try clothes ...
Por ejemplo, si el otro día tuve que hacerme probarme una ropa...
我正在发送照片，也许他告诉我，在那件衬衫下面穿着衬衫尝试。
And I was sending photos and maybe he told me, tried with a shirt below that shirt.
y yo le iba mandando fotos y a lo mejor me decía, probá con una remera abajo de esa camisa.
哦，还有另一只鞋子。
Oh, with another shoe.
Oh, con otro zapato.
你有清晰吗？
Do you have it clear?
¿La tiene clara?
是的，我听她的话。
Yes, I listen to her.
Sí, yo la escucho.
另一个是曾经用过的头发，妈妈，对吗？
And the other is the hair, which was used to be used, mom, right?
Y la otra es el pelo, que antes se usaba de gradation, mamá, ¿no?
好吧，我认为，如果它是在本赛季开始时，我不知道它会开始使用它。
Well, I don't know how much it makes you start using it, if it was at the beginning of the season, I think.
Bueno, no sé cuánto hace que lo empiece a usar, si fue al principio de temporada, creo.
我不记得，我说...我厌倦了去美发师。
I didn't remember, I said ... I had tired of going to the hairdresser.
No me acuerdo, dije... Me había cansado de ir al peluquero.
啊，这就是原因。
Ah, that's why.
Ah, fue por eso.
他说，我不想去美发师。
I don't want to go to the hairdresser, he said.
No quiero ir más al peluquero, decía.
所有阿根廷的孩子都说，降级不再消失了，保罗不使用降解。
All Argentina's kids say, the degrade does not go anymore, Paulo does not use the degradic.
Todos los pibes de Argentina dicen, no va más el degradé, Paulo no usa más el degradé.
离开很长时间，显然您会减少它，因为如果不是以后，它就会想到。
Leaving long, obviously you reduce it because if not later it comes to mind.
a dejar largo, obviamente te lo rebajo porque si no después te viene a la cabeza así.
例如，梅西。
For example, Messi.
Por ejemplo, Messi.
当然，狮子座也开始离开。
Of course, Leo began to leave too.
Claro, Leo se empezó a dejar largo también.
宽阔。
By the wide.
Pelo largo.
也阅读。
And read too.
Y Lea también.
一开始的那一天，我搞砸了Vincha。
The day at the beginning I screwed with the Vincha.
El día al principio me jodía con la vincha.
他告诉我，你是谁，拉法·纳达尔（Rafa Nadal）链接？
He told me, who are you, Rafa Nadal, to be linking?
Me decía, ¿a quién sos, Rafa Nadal, que seas vincha?
我说，如果它不打扰我，那么这个和其他花了两个月，我就接受了点击培训。
I say, if it doesn't bother me, this and the other spent two months, I was with a click training.
Le digo, es que si no me molesta, esto y lo otro pasaron dos meses, estaba con un pinche entrenando.
哦，你不知道，我想杀死他。
Oh, you don't know, I wanted to kill him.
Ah, no sabés, lo quería matar.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
我要问你人们向我们发送的问题。
I'm going to ask you questions that people sent us.
Te voy a hacer preguntas que nos mandó la gente.
我要选择一对。
I'm going to choose a couple.
Voy a elegir un par.
EMI Origlia的第一个。
The first of Emi Origlia.
La primera de Emi Origlia.
帕勃罗，您知道如何在房子里做事，烹饪类型，组装家具，涂墙吗？
Pablo, do you know how to do things in the house, cooking type, assemble furniture, paint the wall?
Pablo, ¿sabés hacer cosas en la casa, tipo cocinar, armar muebles, pintar la pared?
很多。
That's a lot.
Eso es mucho.
厨师。
Cook.
Cocinar.
我把家具放在一起。
I put together a furniture.
Te armo un mueble.
啊，是吗？
Ah, yes?
¿Ah, sí?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
你给自己躁狂吗？
Do you give yourself Mania?
¿Te das mania?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
到...来放一些...给你耐心。
To ... come and put there a little of ... to give you patience.
A que te... Que venga y le metes ahí un poquito de... A que te dé paciencia.
绘画和那东西。
Painting and that thing.
pintar y esa cosa.
Cosina和...
Cosina and ...
Cosina y...
基本的。
Basic.
Básico.
厨房，是的。
Kitchen, yes.
Cocina, sí.
我让你成为糊状和米兰人，但是...
I make you a paste and a milanese, but ...
Te hago una pasta y una milanesa, pero...
做一个食谱，我必须寻找它...和Oriana？
Make a recipe, I have to look for it ... And Oriana?
Hacer una receta, la tengo que buscar... ¿Y Oriana?
它发生了变化，更实用。
It is shifted, it is more practical.
Se da maña, se oriana más práctica.
在两种美食中，比你更多。
Of the two cuisine more than you.
De los dos cocina más ella que vos.
煮更多她。
Cook more she.
Cocina más ella.
埃米尔（Emile）问，您还记得更多的目标？
Emile asks, what goal do you remember with more love?
Emile pregunta, ¿qué gol tuyo recordás con más cariño?
它不一定是您实现的最佳目标，而是您记得时记得微笑的目标。
It cannot necessarily be the best goal you made, but a goal that you remember taking a smile when you remember.
No necesariamente puede ser el mejor gol que hiciste, sino un gol que recuerdes que te saca una sonrisa cuando te acordás.
您选择哪一个？
Which one do you choose?
¿Cuál elegís?
您可以成为巴勒莫研究所。
You can be an institute, Palermo.
Podés ser Instituto, Palermo.
我也参加你的选择。
I go in your selection too.
Yo voy en tu selección también.
我有两个。
I have two.
Tengo dos.
我一直更喜欢第一个，与研究所一起前进。
I have always preferred the first, with institute, head on.
Siempre he preferido el primero, con instituto, de cabeza encima.
我在职业生涯中取得了两个或三个目标。
I have made two or three goals in my career.
que he hecho dos o tres goles de cabeza en mi carrera.
那是谁？
Who was that against?
¿Contra quién fue ese?
你是否记得？
Do you remember?
¿Te acordás?
contra aldo sibi。
Contra Aldo Sibi.
是第一个吗？
Was it the first?
¿Fue el primero?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
在朱夫（Juve）的同时，还有另一个对国际阵线的反对。
And there is another against Inter, for Juve, at the time of Covid.
y hay otro contra el Inter, para la Juve, en la época del Covid.
那个目标是如何的？
How was that goal?
¿Cómo fue ese gol?
然后我钩住，我开始前往中间，我用拉姆齐拍了墙。
And I hook, I start going to the middle, I shoot a wall with Ramsey.
Y engancho, empiezo a ir para el medio, tiro una pared con Ramsey.
那很好。
That's nice.
Ese por lindo.
因为这也是我们正在与比赛进行战斗的时刻，我们开始搬走。
Because it was also a moment that we were fighting the tournament and there we started to move away.
porque fue también un momento que estábamos ahí peleando el torneo y ahí nos empezamos a alejar.
您有多少修改或有多少干扰有信心，如果您有运动员或运动员能够将其估算到法庭上？
How much modifies or how much interference does you have the confidence that if you have an athlete or player to be able to estimate it to the court?
¿Cuánto modifica o cuanta injerencia tiene la confianza que si tiene uno como deportista o jugador para poder estralarlo a la cancha?
100％。
100%.
100％？
¿100%?
100％。
100%.
这是最重要的事情之一。
It is one of the most important things.
Es de las cosas más importantes.
是的，信任。
Yes, trust.
Sí, la confianza.
碰巧的是，有时我看到一个没有出色比赛的球员是一个目标，他是另一个球员。
It happens a lot that I see it sometimes a player who is not having a good game makes a goal, he is another player.
Pasa mucho que yo lo veo a veces un jugador que no está teniendo un buen partido hace un gol, es otro jugador.
它改变了你。
It changes you.
te cambia.
我觉得那样。
I feel like that.
Yo lo siento así.
并且在选择中也必须发生。
And in the selection that must also have happened.
Y en la selección también debe haber pasado eso.
因为他们的表现很好，所以他缺乏冠冕。
Because they played well, he lacked to crown.
porque jugaban bien, le faltaba coronar.
Coronan，Change Trust。
Coronan, change trust.
Coronan, cambia la confianza.
它已发布。
It is released.
Se libera.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
还有一些技术人员比其他玩家更好地工作，您还记得什么？
And there are technicians who work better that than others with the players, what do you remember?
¿Y hay técnicos que laburan mejor eso que otros con los jugadores, que vos recuerdes?
是的，是的，是的。
Yes, yes, yes.
Sí, sí, sí.
您发生了哪一个？
Which one did that happen to you?
¿Con cuál te pasó eso?
也就是说，个人心情吗？
That is, does the personal, mood?
Es decir, ¿te labura bien la parte personal, anímica?
好吧，埃斯卡洛尼（Escaloni）在他的职业生涯初期工作。
Well, Escaloni works at the beginning of his career.
Bueno, Escaloni trabaja al principio de su carrera.
我努力与球员交谈，这给球队带来了很大的信心。
I worked hard to talk to the player and that gave a lot of confidence to the team.
Yo trabajaba muchísimo de hablar con el jugador y eso le daba mucha confianza al equipo.
做得很好，玩家感到舒适。
To do things well and the player feels comfortable.
para hacer las cosas bien y que el jugador se sienta cómodo.
与达里奥·佛朗哥（Dario Franco）一起说话，我几乎没有开始。
With Dario Franco, he spoke a lot, I barely started.
Con Dario Franco hablaba muchísimo, apenas arranqué.
我为我提供了很多建议，对我而言，这是全新的，所以...
I advised me a lot and for me it was all new, so ...
me aconsejaba muchísimo y para mí al principio era todo nuevo, entonces...
Para Miron Plus。
Para Miron Plus.
para Miron Plus.
但是，那么技术人员的工作更多，教练的工作较少。
But well, then the coach works more, the coach works less.
Pero bueno, después el técnico trabaja más, el técnico trabaja menos.
拉尼里（Ranieri）。
Ranieri too.
Ranieri también.
我说的是一名心理学家比教练多次。
More a psychologist, I said that several times, than a coach.
más un psicólogo, eso lo dije varias veces, que un entrenador.
我几次触摸了我与Escaloni交谈的视频，这使我再次再次发送给我
I have touched me several times that the video that I am talking to Escaloni that makes that day again send me again
a mí me ha tocado varias veces que me mandan nuevamente el vídeo que yo estoy hablando con Escaloni que hace ese día
他喜欢他包裹你，我不知道积极的东西
And he like he wrapped you and I don't know something positive
y él como que te arropa y ahí no sé sacó algo positivo
反对哥伦比亚，对吗？
Against Colombia, right?
Contra Colombia fue, ¿no?
反对哥伦比亚。
Against Colombia.
Contra Colombia.
你穿哥伦比亚衬衫吗？
Are you with a Colombian shirt?
¿Vos estabas con una remera de Colombia?
是的，我穿着哥伦比亚衬衫。
Yes, I was with a Colombian shirt.
Sí, yo estaba con una remera de Colombia.
是的，是的，我记得，我记得。
Yes, yes, I remember, I remember.
Sí, sí, me acuerdo, me acuerdo.
必须有一点，与他拥有的球员的距离。
There that must be a bit, the proximity to the player he has.
Ahí debe ser un poco eso, la cercanía al jugador que tiene.
好吧，那时，几乎没有可不同的性能，但是我最近玩了。
Well, at that time, for little differentiability, but I had recently played.
Bueno, en ese momento, por poca diferenciabilidad, pero había jugado hace poco.
这个音符有多好！
How good this note comes!
¡Qué buena viene esta nota!
作为10岁的城市，拥有历史，充满了人们，拥有一切。
As the city, which is a 10, has history, full of people, has everything.
Como la ciudad, que es un 10, tiene historia, llena de gente, tiene todo.
除了罗马，我们缺少任何东西，因为我们去了货物。
Apart from Rome, we were missing anything because we went to eat at the fret.
Aparte de Roma no nos faltó nada porque fuimos a comer al Trastevere.
我们去了罗马竞技场，我们去了委内兹广场。
We went to the Colosseum, we went to Piazza Venezia.
Fuimos al Coliseo, fuimos a Piazza Venezia.
虚弱的La Fontana di Trevi。
INFALTABLE LA FONTANA DI TREVI.
infaltable la Fontana di Trevi.
我们去那里吃饭是因为人们告诉我们，事实是他们使我们成为一个很好的建议。
We went to eat there because people told us and the truth that they made us a very good recommendation.
A comer ahí fuimos porque la gente nos lo dijo y la verdad que nos hicieron una recomendación buenísima.
这就是为什么值得推荐的原因。
That is why it is worth recommending something.
Por eso vale la pena que le recomendemos algo.
热门销售非常接近，但是在德克斯特，已经有最好的促销。
The Hot Sale is very close, but in Dexter there are already the best promos.
El Hot Sale está muy cerca, pero en Dexter ya están las mejores promos.
从5月5日至11日，您需要的一切最多可享受60％的折扣。
From May 5 to 11 you have up to 60% discount on everything you need.
Del 5 al 11 de mayo tenés hasta un 60% de descuento en todo lo que necesitas.
巴黎去健身房跑步。
Paris to the gym to run.
París al gimnasio para salir a correr.
无论您想要什么，要训练，衣服，鞋类。
To train, clothing, footwear, whatever you want.
para entrenar, indumentaria, calzado, lo que quieras.
因此，您知道，在dexter.com.ar上走车并准备。
So you know, walk the cart at Dexter.com.ar and prepare.
Así que ya sabes, anda preparando el carrito en Dexter.com.ar y prepárate.
德克斯特是运动。
Dexter is sport.
Dexter es deporte.
如果您愿意的话，请剪切，也可以来自阿根廷国家队
Cut if you respond short if you want can also be from the Argentine National Team
corta si responde corto si quieres también puede ser de la selección argentina
我们通常喜欢您的职业生涯，因为有时外国球员说阿根廷的人们没有这样的人，而且很好。
We like your career in general because sometimes a foreign player speaks that people in Argentina do not have so at hand and it is good.
de tu carrera en general también nos gusta porque a veces habla de un jugador extranjero que la gente en Argentina no tiene tan a mano y está bueno.
伴侣扮演整个职业生涯的诀窍，而不仅仅是选择。
A partner to play the trick of your entire career, not just the selection.
un compañero para jugar al truco de toda tu carrera, no solamente de la selección.
你选择谁？
Who do you choose?
¿A quién elegís?
Lea。
Lea.
是的，您最了解自己。
Yes, with whom you understand yourself the most.
Sí, con quien más te entendés.
是的，前几天我在...
Yes, the other day I was in ...
Sí, el otro día estaba en...
在一个生日，我无法去打电话给我，请告诉我我们必须扮演这个技巧。
On a birthday that I had not been able to go and called me and please told me that we have to play the trick.
en un cumpleaños que yo no había podido ir y me llamaba y me decía por favor vení que tenemos que jugar el truco.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
我知道他不会在选择中选择我，但是在这里他必须选择我。
I know that he will not choose me in the selection, but here he has to choose me.
Yo sé que él en la selección no me va a elegir, pero acá me tiene que elegir.
在这里，您必须选择您。
Here you have to choose you.
Acá te tiene que elegir.
你还是不是？
And were you or not?
¿Y fuiste o no?
不，我不是。
No, I wasn't.
No, no fui.
你不是。
You weren't.
No fuiste.
伴侣带伴侣和聊天。
A partner to take mates and chat of life.
Un compañero para tomar mates y charlar de la vida.
愿有趣的。
May it be interesting.
Que sea interesante.
与我分享了许多伴侣的同伴。
Companion with whom I shared many mates.
compañero con el que compartí muchos mates.
几乎每天都有静音草莓。
Almost every day, with the mute strawberry.
Casi todos los días, con el Mudo Vasque.
与静音草莓。
With the mute strawberry.
Con el Mudo Vasque.
那说话不多。
That does not speak much.
Que no habla mucho.
是的，先生。
Yes sir.
Sí, señor.
但是当我们一个人...
But when we were alone ...
Pero cuando estábamos solos...
我说了很多，是的。
I spoke a lot, yes.
Hablaba un montón, sí.
那时不再保持沉默。
There was no longer silent then.
Ahí ya no era mudo entonces.
还有一个再次玩？
And one to play again?
¿Y uno para volver a jugar?
您喜欢分享法院并说我想再次玩。
That you liked to share the court and say I want to play again with.
que te haya gustado compartir la cancha y decir quiero volver a jugar con.
它可以情绪激动，也可能是足球。
It can be emotional or can be football.
Puede ser emocional o puede ser futbolístico.
丹妮·阿尔维斯（Dani Alves）。
Dani Alves.
游戏。
Game.
Juegabrazo.
一个伴侣，如果是给您的，您会将阿根廷国有化，告诉我这一点，我把它带给我，您已经分享了。
A partner who, if it were for you, you would nationalize Argentine, who tell me this, I bring it to me, that you have shared.
un compañero que, si fuese por vos, nacionalizarías argentino, que decís este me lo traigo para mí, que hayas compartido.
因为？
Because?
¿Por qué?
为什么
Why
Por por qué.
这是一个现象。
It was a phenomenon.
Era un fenómeno.
偷窃的人是我们之前谈论时尚的勒克斯
And someone who steals is lux that we talk about fashion before
y alguno que le robe es lux que antes hablamos de la moda que fue si se te está haciendo
它到达了所有完美的地方。
It reaches all the perfect places.
Llega a todos los lugares perfecto.
在罗马，没有那么多。
Here in Rome there is not so much.
Acá en la Roma no hay tanto.
但是他没有偷走洛洛，但他在马奎西奥雨中经常看着他。
But he did not stole Lolo, but he looked at him a lot in the Marquicio rain.
pero no le robó a Lolo, pero le miraba mucho en la lluvia Marquicio.
当然，侯爵夫人。
Marquise, of course.
Marquise, claro.
我几乎每天都穿着西装。
I was almost in a suit every day.
Iba casi de traje todos los días.
在西装培训中？
In suit training?
¿En el entrenamiento de traje?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
穿西装？
In a suit?
¿De traje?
好像是办公室。
As if it were an office.
Como si fuera una oficina.
这有点玩。
This is a bit played.
Esta es un poco jugada.
一个伴侣，会让他剪你的头发。
A partner who would let him cut your hair.
Un compañero que lo dejarías cortarte el pelo.
你不会错。
You cannot be wrong.
No se puede equivocar.
您在这个信任中说什么不会让我感到震惊。
What do you say in this trust will not shit me.
Que decís en este confío no me va a cagar.
必须是一个认真的人，对吗？
It has to be someone serious, right?
Tiene que ser alguien serio, ¿no?
可靠的。
Reliable.
Confiable.
是他是一个bit子的儿子。
Is that he is a very son of a bitch.
Es que es un muy hijo de puta.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
我想我在想GIO。
I'm thinking of Gio, I think.
Estoy pensando en Gio, creo.
他留下了镇定，离开了。
He leaves calm, he leaves.
Se va tranquilo, se va serio.
还有一个永远不会让他拯救头发的伴侣？
And a partner who would never let him save his hair?
¿Y un compañero que nunca le dejaría guardar el pelo?
WHO？
Who?
¿Quién?
罗德里戈。
Rodrigo.
Rodri.
它使你成为邪恶。
It makes you an evil.
Te hace una maldad.
罗德里（Rodri）和莱（Lea）也在那里。
Rodri and Lea is also there to the limit.
Rodri y Lea también está ahí al límite.
在您的职业或生活中一直在等待的事情。
Something that has been pending in your career or in your life.
algo que te haya quedado pendiente en tu carrera o en tu vida.
嗯...
Eh...
在我的职业生涯中，我失去了冠军联赛决赛的厄运。
In my career I had the bad luck of losing the final of the Champions League.
En mi carrera tuve la mala suerte de perder final de Champions y final de Europa League.
你有吗？
Did you have?
¿Te quedó?
我会喜欢的，是的。
I would have liked, yes.
Me hubiese gustado, sí.
但是也...
But also...
Pero también...
我非常接近与该研究所的崛起，那一年真是令人难以置信。
I was very close to ascending with the institute, which would have been incredible that year.
estuve muy cerca de ascender con el instituto, que hubiese sido increíble ese año.
也就是说，赢得了冠军或欧罗巴联赛，并登上了研究所。
That is, winning Champions or Europa League and ascending to the institute as well.
Es decir, ganar Champions o Europa League y ascender al Instituto también.
您将其放在同一级别。
You put it there at the same level.
Lo pones ahí al mismo nivel.
这三个在每个地方。
And the three are in each place.
Y las tres son en cada lugar.
我为升级学院代表的是尤文图斯的代表。
What I would have represented for the Ascending Institute is a bit what would have represented for Juventus.
Lo que hubiese representado para el Instituto Ascender es un poco lo que hubiese representado para la Juventus.
赢得冠军，并为罗马赢得欧罗巴联赛。
Win the Champions and for Rome win the Europa League.
ganar la Champions y para la Roma ganar la Europa League.
您是否有研究所的粉丝科尔多瓦（Cordoba），有时会在意大利旅行或estende度假，并会看到您或放旗？
Do you have an institute fan, Cordoba, who sometimes travels in Italy or Estende Vacation and will see you or put a flag?
¿Tienes un hincha de instituto, cordobeses, que a veces viaja en Italia o estende vacaciones y te vayan a ver o te pongan una bandera?
是的，有时是。
Yes, sometimes yes.
Sí, a veces sí.
它还发生在您身上吗？
Is it still happening to you?
¿Te sigue pasando?
是的，是的，我不得不在法庭上看到Institute Flag。
Yes, yes, I had to see institute flag on the court.
Sí, sí, me ha pasado ver bandera de instituto en la cancha.
在罗马，比其他地方更多，但有时他们会离开法庭，他们告诉你，我来自科尔达，研究所。
More here in Rome than in other places, but sometimes leaving the court they tell you, I am from Corda, Institute.
más acá en la Roma que en otros lugares, pero a veces saliendo de la cancha te dicen, yo soy de corda, instituto.
好吧，让我们看看您对您有多了解，您将确认是否错误，因为您应该知道。
Well, let's see how much you know about you with some questions and you will corroborate whether or not it was wrong because you should know.
Bueno, a ver cuánto sabés de vos con algunas preguntas y vos corrobarás si se equivocó o no porque deberías saberlo.
不，我会在这里暴露。
No, I will be exposed here.
No, pará, voy a quedar expuesto acá.
好的。
Ok.
首先是...您已经做对了。
The first is ... You already got it right.
La primera es... Ya la acertaste.
您在第一版中的第一个进球，负责人的头。
Your first goal in the first edition, the head of the head.
Tu primer gol en primera edición, el docibe de cabeza.
您在俱乐部中有多少个目标和助攻？
How many goals and assists do you have in the clubs?
¿Cuántos goles y asistencias tenés en los clubes?
在这里，我杀了你，因为我们最近在寻找它。
Here I kill you because we look for it recently.
Acá te mato porque lo buscamos hace poco.
但是我们在助攻方面有问题，一个地方说一个又一个，但我们已经看到了。
But we have a problem with the assists, which in one place says one and another, but we had seen.
Pero tenemos un problema con las asistencias, que en un lugar dice una y en otro otro, pero habíamos visto.
199个目标和99个股票。
199 goals and 99 stocks.
199 goles y 99 existencias.
完美，这是俱乐部及其...
Perfect, here is clubs and its ...
Perfecto, acá está clubes y su...
因为他们没有计算学院，而前几天他们看到了派对，我认为有七个。
Because they did not count the institutes and the other day they saw the institutes parties and I think there were seven.
Porque no contaban las de institutos y el otro día vieron los partidos de institutos y creo que eran siete.
在整个职业生涯中，您做了多少个技巧？
And how many Tricks hack did you do throughout your career?
¿Y cuántos hack tricks hiciste a lo largo de tu carrera?
如果您还记得他们是谁。
And if you remember who they were.
Y si te acordás a quiénes fueron.
我在阿根廷做了两个，无家可归和亚特兰大。
I made two in Argentina, homeless and Atlanta.
Hice dos en Argentina, Desamparado y Atlanta.
正确的。
Correct.
Correcto.
我在冠军中对年轻男孩做了一个。
I did one in Champions against Young Boys.
Hice uno en Champions contra el Young Boys.
一个对阵都灵，一个对阵萨苏洛，一个对阵热那亚。
One against Torino, one against Sassuolo, one against Genoa.
Uno contra el Torino, uno contra el Sassuolo, uno contra el Genoa.
您失踪了，您无可挑剔。
You are missing, you are impeccable.
Te falta uno, estás impecable.
你想念一个吗？
Are you missing one?
¿Te falta uno solo?
你失踪了。
You are missing.
Uno te falta.
与尤文图斯在一起？
¿With Juventus?
¿Con la Juventus?
与尤文图斯。
With Juventus.
Con Juventus.
团队...有土壤。
A team ... There is soil.
Un equipo... Se da suelo.
热那亚。
Genoa.
还有一个。
And one more.
Y una más.
约翰·博伊斯（John Boyce），都灵。
John Boyce, Torino.
我缺少一个。
I lack one.
Me falta uno.
是的，这可以通过A系列或Coppa Italia悄悄地进行。
Yes, this can be quietly by series A or Coppa Italia.
Sí, esto puede ser tranquilamente por Serie A o Coppa Italia.
我不知道这两个中的哪个。
I don't know which of the two.
No sé cuál de las dos.
奇科队。
Chico team.
Equipo chico.
你删除了猫吗？
Did you delete a cat?
¿Te borraste un gato?
是意大利杯拥抱你吗？
Was it Copa Italia hugged you?
¿Fue Copa Italia te abrazó?
好吧，最后。
Well, and the last.
Bueno, y la última.
在选择中首次亮相。
Debut in the selection.
Debute en la selección.
与哪个竞争对手以及您进入谁，因为您在银行里。
Against which rival and who you entered, because you were in the bank.
contra qué rival y por quién entraste, porque estabas en el banco.
Carlitos Tevez对游客的巴拉圭。
by Carlitos Tevez against Paraguay of visitors.
por Carlitos Tevez contra Paraguay de visitantes.
出色的。
Excellent.
Excelente.
你还记得一切吗？
Do you remember everything?
¿Te acordás todo?
你有记忆吗？
Do you have memory for that?
¿Tenés memoria para eso?
我救了你，因为...你不知道哪一个？
I save you because ... which one you did not know?
Me salvo a vos porque... ¿Cuál no te sabías?
hacktick。
The Hacktick.
La del hacktrick.
黑客没有机会。
The Hacktick there was no chance.
La del hacktrick no había chance.
我没机会，我想起了约翰·男孩，但其余的没有。
There was no chance, I remembered John Boy, but the rest did not.
No había chance, me acordaba de John Boy, pero el resto no.
它将记住您的目标。
It is going to remember your goals.
Es irse a acordar de tus goles.
您有记忆的记忆还是不感兴趣？
Do you have memory for yours or are you not interested?
¿Tenés memoria para lo tuyo o no te interesa?
是的，是的，但是如果你问我约会，你杀了我。
Yes, yes, but if you ask me dates, you kill me.
Sí, sí, pero si me preguntas fechas, me matas.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
如果您告诉我我会在什么日期首次亮相，我发誓我不记得了。
If you tell me what date I would have debuted, I swear I don't remember.
Si me decís qué fecha hubiese debutado, te juro que no me acuerdo.
但是，是的，我记得游戏，目标，谁是谁。
But yes, the games, the goals, who was, I remember.
pero sí, los partidos, los goles, quién estaba, sí me acuerdo.
但是到目前为止，我很糟糕。
But to date I am very bad.
Pero a la fecha soy muy malo.
帕勃罗，最后一个问题。
Pablo, last questions.
Pablo, últimas preguntas.
发生了卡塔尔发生的...
Is Catar happened ...
¿Ya pasó Catar...
2022年，当然，这是如此强烈，我们相信我们继续将其设在附近，但事实是，世界杯的时代已经过去了，我们正在...
2022, of course, it was so strong that we believe that we continue to have it nearby, but the truth is that a time of the World Cup has passed and we are ...
2022, claro, fue tan fuerte que nosotros creemos que lo seguimos teniendo cerca, pero la verdad que ya pasó un tiempo del mundial y estamos...
以世界价格一年。
A year at world price.
a un año de Precio Mundial.
什么产生了？
What generates that?
¿Qué te genera eso?
我想问一下您是否继续野心扮演Mundel，因为最终您已经实现了它并离开了冠军。
I want to ask you if you continued to go to the ambition to play a mundel because in the end you already fulfilled it and left champion.
Quiero preguntarte si seguiste yendo a la ambición de jugar un Mundel porque al final ya lo cumpliste y saliste campeón.
好吧，如果您期望这样，您在说什么，什么会造成您的影响？
And well, if you expect to be, what are you talking about, what generates you?
Y bueno, si esperás estar, qué hablas, ¿qué te genera?
不，显而易见，显而易见的是...
No, obvious, obvious that one ...
No, obvio, obvio que uno...
他总是想成为。
He always wants to be.
siempre quiere estar.
对我来说，在足球一级存在的最漂亮的比赛。
The prettiest competition that exists at the football level for me.
la competición más linda que existe a nivel futbolístico para mí.
然后，显然，在卡塔尔取得的成就是...
And then what was achieved in Qatar, obviously, to relive it would be ...
y después lo que se logró en Catar, obviamente, que revivirlo sería...
会很漂亮。
It would be beautiful.
Sería hermoso.
这并不容易，因为正如我一直说的那样，阿根廷队有
It is not easy because, as I always say, the Argentine team has
No es fácil porque, como digo siempre, la selección argentina tiene
球员的粉丝如此之大，以至于比赛是巨大的。
A fan of players so big that the competition is huge.
Un abanico de jugadores tan grande que la competición es enorme.
是的...
Y...
这也使得必须在俱乐部中100％的表现才能达到。
And that also makes one have to perform 100% in their club to be able to be.
y eso también hace que uno tenga que rendir al 100% en su club para poder estar.
因此，对我来说，这是一个动机。
So, for me it is a motivation.
Entonces, para mí es una motivación.
知道我在这里做得很好。
Have it so close to knowing that if I do things well here.
tenerlo tan cerca de saber de que si hago las cosas bien acá.
我有可能再次参加世界杯，显然我会尽一切可能...
I have the possibility of being in a World Cup again and obviously I will do everything possible to ...
tengo la posibilidad de volver a estar en un Mundial y obviamente que voy a hacer todo lo posible para...
能够。
To be able to be.
para poder estar.
那将是教练的决定。
Then it will be a decision of the coach.
Después va a ser una decisión del entrenador.
尽力而为或相信自己是...
to take the best or those who believe they are ...
de llevar a los mejores o a los que crea que son...
最好的竞争和等待，但是显然，让他们如此亲密是一个动力。
The best to compete and wait, but obviously that having them so close is a motivation.
los mejores para competir y esperar, pero obviamente que teniéndolos tan cerca es una motivación.
从即将到来的赛季前开始做事。
Start doing things well from the pre -season that comes.
empezar a hacer las cosas bien desde la pretemporada que viene.
精确的。
Exact.
Exacto.
好吧，我们向您展示这张照片。
Well, we show you this photo.
Bueno, te mostramos esta foto.
让我们看看，它在那里。
Let's see, it's there.
A ver, está ahí.
它带给您什么回忆？
What memories does it bring you?
¿Qué recuerdos te trae?
在这里，您与一群朋友一起返回。
Here you had returned with a group of friends.
Acá habías vuelto con un grupo de amigos.
普约尔，我们告诉老师。
Pujol, we told the teacher.
Pujol, le decíamos al profe.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
好吧，佛朗哥，不是很多...
Well, Franco, not with him a lot that ...
Bueno, Franco, no con él hace muchísimo que...
我不说话，我看不到。
I don't speak, I don't see it.
No hablo, no lo veo.
我每天都在讲Naul。
With Naul I speak every day.
Con Naúl hablo todos los días.
他是一个离开的朋友，甚至与我一起工作，我们做了一些事情。
He is a friend who had left, who even works with me, we do some things.
Es un amigo que me quedó, que incluso trabaja conmigo, hacemos algunas cosas.
好吧，老师，chanito，也没有...
Well, the teacher, the Chanito, who also do not have ...
Bueno, el Profe, el Chanito, que también no tengo...
我没有与他交流。
I have no communication with him.
No tengo comunicación con él.
卢卡斯（Lucas）的兄弟FedeBeltrán在研究所一起演奏。
Fede Beltrán, Lucas's brother, who played together at the institute.
Fede Beltrán, el hermano de Lucas, que jugábamos juntos en el instituto.
他不太好，
He is not more good and
el no está más bueno y
那个瘦的人告诉他，他仍在与bolifea接触，我一次看到它...
The skinny one told him that he is still in contact with a Bolifea and I have seen it once in ...
La flaca le decíamos que sigue en contacto con una bolifea y lo he visto una vez en...
在科尔多巴，但我很久没有和他说话了，古斯蒂·盖蒂（Gusti Goti）
In Córdoba, but I haven't talked to him for a long time, and Gusti Goti, who was one of
en Córdoba, pero hace mucho que no hablo con él, y Gusti Goti, que fue uno de
我最好的朋友
Of my best friends in the lower ...
de mis mejores amigos en la inferiores de...
研究所。
of institute.
de instituto.
您仍然达成协议...是的，其中几个是的。
You still have a deal with ... yes, with several of them yes.
Tenés todavía trato con... Sí, con varios de ellos sí.
然后我们想向你展示这个，我不知道，巴贝食物吗？
And then we wanted to show you this one, I don't know, Babay Food?
Y después te queríamos mostrar esta que es, no sé, ¿Babay Food?
是的，它几乎没有开始。
Yes, it was barely started.
Sí, era apenas arrancaba.
我不知道。
I don't know.
No sé.
四年，五年，计算出来，是一所小学校，非常离家很近。
Four years, five, calculated and was a little school that was very close to home.
cuatro años, cinco, calculo y era una escuelita que quedaba muy cerca de casa.
在那个年龄，这是我们在一个很小的小镇中唯一拥有的。
And that at that age it was the only one we had in a very small town.
y que a esa edad era la única que teníamos en un pueblo muy chiquito.
我们已经有十五岁的15个孩子。
We had been ten, fifteen children who played there.
Habíamos sido diez, quince nenes que jugábamos ahí.
但是在这里，您追求睡眠。
But here you pursued sleep.
Pero acá perseguías el sueño.
在那里，我们试图赢得奖杯。
And there we try to win, to have trophies.
Y ahí ya tratamos de ganar, de tener trofeos.
您会看到，在一天的漩涡中，有时会失去您想要的东西的概念，因为您想要更多，因为一切都会很快发生。
You saw that in the maelstrom of day to day one sometimes loses notion of what you get because you want more, because everything happens very fast.
Viste que en la vorágine del día a día uno a veces pierde noción de lo que consigue porque querés más, porque pasa todo muy rápido.
是什么让您看到这些照片？
What generates you to see those photos?
¿Qué te genera ver esas fotos?
谈论你们所有的朋友。
Talk about your friends who were all there.
Hablar de tus amigos que estaban todos ahí.
然后，好吧，我们在这里聊天，您是阿根廷追随者的意大利足球人物。
And then, well, we are talking here and you are an Italian football figure, of the Argentine follower.
Y después, bueno, estamos hablando acá y vos sos una figura del fútbol italiano, de la Seguidora Argentina.
有片刻你停下来说...
Are there moments where you stop and say ...
¿Hay momentos donde te detenés y decís...
看看我在哪里，看看我的生活，我拥有的生活。
Look where I am, look at the life I had, the one I have.
Mirar donde estoy, mirar la vida que tuve, la que tengo.
我不知道您是否动员，如果您说话，
I don't know if you mobilize, if you talk, that or not.
No sé si te moviliza, si lo hablás, eso o no.
是的，有时候，好吧...
Yes, sometimes, well ...
Sí, a veces, bueno...
与Fede和Nahuel一起，我几乎每天都会说话，我们总是会说话，因为
With Fede and Nahuel that are the ones with which I speak almost every day and we always speak it because
con Fede y Nahuel que son los con los que hablo casi todos los días y siempre lo hablamos porque
从我们从下层学院开始到...
We made the same path, from the ten years that we started together at the lower institute to the ...
Hicimos el mismo camino, desde los diez años que empezamos juntos en la inferior instituto hasta los...
17我第一个去，我们一起旅行。
17 That I went up to First, we were traveling together.
17 que yo subí a primera, viajábamos juntos.
我们聚在一起，每天训练，我们一起玩FA，一切。
We got together, we trained every day, we played FA together, everything.
Nos juntábamos, entrenábamos todos los días, jugábamos al FA juntos, todo.
我总是说，我很幸运能触摸我，我可以触摸他...
And I always say, I was lucky that I have touched me, I could have touched him ...
Y yo siempre digo, yo tuve la suerte de que me haya tocado a mí, le podría haber tocado...
他们中的任何一个，但达里奥·佛朗哥（Dario Franco）只是来了。
Any of them too, but Dario Franco came just.
a cualquiera de ellos también, pero justo se dio que llegó Dario Franco.
他喜欢我的游戏，有时您需要一点运气，因为最好的事情会来了。
He liked my game and sometimes you need a little luck because the best would have come.
le gustó mi juego y a veces necesitas un poco de suerte porque lo mejor hubiese venido.
在这种情况下，任何其他教练，也许他喜欢Nahuel的比赛，Gusti或Fede或任何其他教练。
Any other coach and maybe he liked Nahuel's game in this case or Gusti or Fede or any other coach.
cualquier otro entrenador y a lo mejor le gustaba más el juego de Nahuel en este caso o de Gusti o de Fede o de cualquier otro entrenador.
男孩和今天最好的是坐在别人的地方，但也很好
of the boys and today the best would be sitting others but well too
de los chicos y hoy lo mejor estaría sentado otros pero bueno también
你必须知道的机会
That opportunity you have to know
esa oportunidad muchas veces hay que saber
利用它，您必须知道如何工作，而不是为...
Take advantage of it, you have to know how to work it, not settle for anything because ...
aprovecharla, hay que saber trabajarla, no conformarse con nada porque...
除了足球比赛，没有人会给你这么多...
No one will give you, except in football, having so many ...
Nadie te regalará, menos en el fútbol, habiendo tantas...
如此之多的球员，如此之多的竞争，然后在这种可能性必须知道的时候。
So much players, so much competition, then one when that possibility has to know.
tanto jugadores, tanta competencia, entonces uno cuando le toca esa posibilidad la tiene que saber.
充分利用它并充分利用它。
Take advantage and exploit it to the fullest.
aprovechar y explotarla al máximo.
那是...的信息
That is the message for the ...
Ese es el mensaje para el...
对于男孩，也许。
For the boys, maybe.
Para los chicos a lo mejor.
因为在那个年龄很难
Because at that age it is difficult, one has many things in the head doing ...
Porque a esa edad es difícil, uno tiene muchas cosas en la cabeza haciendo...
少年在15、16和今天...
teenager at 15, 16 and today ...
adolescente a los 15, 16 y hoy...
在我们15-16的阿根廷足球中，您必须成为。
In our Argentine football at 15-16 you have to be.
En nuestro fútbol argentino a los 15-16 tenés que estar.
很快，因为它可以随时触摸您，所以在这里并不预期的是，他们说不，还没有。
Soon because it can touch you at any time, it is not like here that it is expected a little more, which they say no, it is not yet.
Ya pronto porque te puede tocar en cualquier momento, no es como acá que se espera un poco más, que dicen no, todavía no está.
16岁时，你必须准备好
At 16 you have to be ready
a los 16 tiene que estar listo
一个刚刚开始成为运动员并追求梦想之外的梦想的男孩会有什么建议或喜悦？
What recommendation or joy does a boy who just starts to be a athlete and who pursues a dream of life beyond playing?
¿Qué recomendación o qué alegría hace un chico que recién arranca a ser deportista y que persigue un sueño de vida más allá de jugar?
您会推荐什么？
What would you recommend?
¿Qué le recomendarías?
嗯...
Eh...
是的，有时候这并不容易。
Yes, sometimes it is not so easy.
Sí, a veces no es tan fácil.
我认为每个人都以某种方式生活...
I think everyone lives it in a way ...
Creo que todos lo viven de manera...
不同，但是我...
different, but me ...
diferente, pero o sea yo...
这让我很长一段时间在牺牲中。
It makes me a long time in the sacrifice.
me hace mucho en el sacrificio.
专注于我想要的东西，而不是转移。
in being focused on what I wanted, not diverting.
en estar enfocado en lo que quería, en no desviarme.
从来没有时间，我年轻的时候...
At no time, when I was younger ...
En ningún momento, cuando era más joven...
您从会议，聚会开始，然后我看到我所有的朋友...
You start with the meetings, the party, then I saw all my friends that ...
Empezás con los cumples, la fiesta, entonces veía a todos mis amigos que...
他们在那一边，所以我知道我的目标是什么，我的梦想要实现以及多么出色...
That they were on that side, so I knew what my goal was, what my dream was to fulfill and how good ...
que iban por ese lado, entonces yo lo sabía cuál era mi objetivo, cuál era mi sueño cumplir y que bueno...
很多次到达一个您必须抛在一边的地方，或者我们想与朋友分享。
That many times to get to a place you have to put things aside that we like or that we would like to do and share with our friends.
que muchas veces para llegar a un lugar hay que dejar cosas de lado que nos gustan o que nos gustaría hacer y compartir con nuestros amigos.
也许之后，以后，时间或生活会让您...
And maybe afterwards, later, time or life will put you ...
y que a lo mejor después, más adelante, el tiempo o la vida te va a poner...
在那个地方，与您的朋友一起享受其他事情。
In that place to enjoy other things with your friends.
en ese lugar para disfrutar otras cosas con tus amigos.
所以我认为...
So I think ...
Entonces yo creo que...
我一生中最发生的单词，我认为是...
The word that happens most in my life and that I think is ...
la palabra que más sucede en mi vida y que creo que es...
当一个人追求梦想（目标）是牺牲时，最重要的词之一。
One of the most important words when one pursues a dream, an objective, is sacrifice.
Una de las palabras más importantes cuando uno persigue un sueño, un objetivo, es el sacrificio.
然后，您可以将其放在不同的事物中，但这是最大的...
Then you can put it in different things, but it's the most ...
Después lo puedes poner en diferentes cosas, pero es lo más...
在我整个职业生涯中发生的最多。
What happens most throughout my career.
lo que más sucede durante toda mi carrera.
不仅在一开始，我仍然使用它。
Not only at the beginning, I still use it to this day.
No solo al principio, lo sigo usando hasta el día de hoy.